Finding Aid to the Gloria Steinem papers SSC.MS.00237
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE, 1954-97
  - Individuals
    - Richards, Ann, undated (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Richey-Rankin, Vel, undated (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Robbins, Jerome, undated (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Robinson, Marianne (Jolly), 1989-90 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Rountree, Cathleen, 1992-93 (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Savitch, Jessica, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Scheinbaum, Stanley, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Schlesinger, Jr., Arthur, 1967-70 (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Schneider, Susan Weidman, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Schroeder, Pat, 1982; 1987; undated (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Shalala, Donna, 1980; 1985 (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - Sheehy, Gail, 1990-94; undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Shephard, Cybill, 1987-88 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Shore, Dinah, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Siegel, Ann, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Liz, 1967-88; undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Sondheim, Stephen, 1967; undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Sorensen, Ted, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Stapleton, Jean, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Stark, Ray, 1968; undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Stein, Robert, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Stern, Elizabeth "Bibsie", 1960-84; undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Stimpson, Katherine, 1987; 1992 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Streep, Meryl, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Styron, William, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Swit, Loretta, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Tannen, Deborah, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Marlo, 1979-84; 1989; 1993; undated (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Tinker, Grant, 1981-84 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Tobias, Sheila, 1982; 1984; 1993; undated (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Tomlin, Lily, 1983; undated (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Trudeau, Gary, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Tutu, Mpho, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Utne, Eric, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Vanderbilt, Gloria, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Van Horn, Edie, 1973-95; undated (Box 90, Folder 25)
      [see also SERIES V. ORGANIZATIONS--National Women's Political Caucus]
    - Van Patten, Joyce, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Walker, Alice, 1974-88; undated (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Wallace, Mike, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Walters, Barbara, 1965; 1979; undated (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Wattleton, Faye, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Willis, Ellen, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Winfrey, Oprah 1987, 1993, n,d. (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Winters, Shelley [see Cyndi Lauper] (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - Wolfe, Tom, 1967 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Zimmerman, Jan; 1984 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - Zuckerman, Mort, 1984; undated (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, 1984-94 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Letters of recommendation 1980-89 [restricted] (Box 91, Folder 2)
- SERIES III. SPEECHES AND APPEARANCES, 1967-93
  Steinem has often recounted her long-held fear of public speaking. The extent of this series is indicative of how well she overcame that fear. Materials here, arranged in three subseries - General, Speech texts, and Radio and television -- include correspondence and publicity materials, speech texts, research materials, and documents pertaining to her travel, such as itineraries and contracts for the continuous stream of public appearances made by Steinem before colleges and university students, political groups, professional organizations, business groups, and bookstore audiences.
  Among the General materials are contracts for appearances, speech research files, and press calls. Of special interest are two folders of cards on which audience members submitted their own questions for Steinem to address during the question and answer period which generally followed her talks. The bulk of the material housed in this subseries, however, documents Steinem's public speaking appearances, largely between 1980 and 1986. They are arranged chronologically, with a general folder for each year followed by folders pertaining to individual appearances. These files may contain correspondence, itineraries, travel receipts, publicity materials, and/or clippings regarding the event.
  Speech texts, far fewer in number, are filed separately and arranged chronologically. Since newspaper coverage often contains excerpts of speeches, researchers interested in the content of Steinem's talks may wish to consult both the speech texts and the files devoted to individual appearances for insight into her comments and speaking style. The larger series of clippings gathered in SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL, may also be of help in this regard. There are also a small number of audiotapes from Steinem's appearances in SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL.
  The final subseries here pertains to Radio and television programs to which Steinem contributed. For just over seven weeks in 1977, Steinem filled in as a substitute commentator on Spectrum, CBS Radio Network's semi-weekly personal opinion series; her commentaries, as well as related correspondence and memoranda, are filed here. Steinem also contributed to two television series: In Conversation With.. and The Today Show. Materials regarding the former include correspondence with Robert Klein as well as research materials pertaining to Steinem's guests (who included, among others, Julian Bond, Coretta Scott King, Andrew Young, and Billie Jean King), and, in some cases, transcripts of Steinem's interviews, including those with Helen Gurley Brown, Phil Donahue, Betty Ford, John Kenneth Galbraith, and Sally Ride. Audiotapes pertaining to several of these interviews can be found in SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL. Materials pertaining to The Today Show include largely correspondence and story ideas.
  - General: lists of appearances, contracts, notes, press calls, question and answer cards, and research materials, 1967-87; undated (Box 92, Folder 1-11)
  - Speaking appearances: correspondence, schedules,clippings, receipts, 1968-1989 (Box 93-99)
  - Texts of speeches (Box 93-99)
    [see also SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL; and SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL - Smith College]
    - Testimony, Senate Hearings on Equal Rights Amendment, 6 May 1970 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - "Living the Revolution," Vassar Commencement Address, 1970 (Box 100)
    - Testimony before New Democratic Coalition Foreign Policy Hearings, 14 September 1971 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - "Why Harvard Law School Needs Women More Than Women Need It," 1971 (includes article version reprinted in the Congressional Record, 23 September 1971 (Box 100)
    - Untitled talk on the Equal Rights Amendment, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - National Press Club, 24 Jan 1972 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Naval Academy, Forrestal Lecture Series, 12 May 1972 (Box 100)
    - "Ms.-Today and Tomorrow," excerpts of talk with Margaret Sloan before staff of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, Dec 1972 (Box 100)
    - League of Women Voters national convention, 1972 (Box 100)
    - "New Life Styles," talk at 2 Aug 1973 Conference on the American Woman, University of Georgia, Athens (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - "America's Need to Know" symposium, New York City, 18 Sep 1973 (Box 100)
    - American Association of Advertising Agencies, Greenbrier, 1973 (Box 100)
    - Simmons College Commencement, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - "The Feminist Revolution," American Association of Advertising Agencies Annual Meeting and Central Region Annual Meeting, 31 Oct 1973 (Box 100)
    - Association of National Advertisers' Media Workshop, 4 Dec 1973 (Box 100)
    - "Are We Open to Change?" speech to Life Insurance AdvertisersAssociation, San Francisco, Oct 1974 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - College of Marin, Kentfield, California, Oct 1974 (Box 100)
    - American Society of Corporate Secretaries National Conference, Puerto Rico, Jun 1974 (Box 100)
    - "But Dear God, Where Are the Women?" International Women's Year Project 1975/Perth, Jan 1975 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - "Statement of the Feminist Movement," Women Unlimited Conference, University of Utah, 16 Oct 1975 (Box 100)
    - PR Conference 4 Sep 1975 (possibly by Pat Carbine) (Box 100)
    - Gender-Based Discrimination and the Equal Rights Amendment, Judicial Conference of the Second Circuit, 11 Sep 1976 (Box 100, Folder 7A)
    - American Marketing Association conference, New York City, 25 Jan 1977 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Statement at IWY Encounter for Journalists, Mexico City, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 8A)
    - St. Louis Community College, St. Louis, MO, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Talk before an unidentified women's conference at the University of Southern California, May 1979 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - National Women's Political Caucus Convention, Cincinnati 15 Jul 1979 (includes introduction by Frances Lear) (Box 100)
    - "Women Against War" conference, New York, 10 Jun 1980 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Welcome for Tatyana Mamonova, 20 Oct 1980 (Box 100, Folder 11A)
    - Economic Democracy, Nov 1981 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - California Nurses Association, Oakland, 10-20 Feb 1982 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Speech nominating Irene Natividad as chair of the National Women's Political Caucus, Biennial convention, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women/ POWER benefit, 28 Jan 1986 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Wheaton College Commencement, 31 May 1986 (Box 101)
    - Cleveland City Club, 1987 (Box 101)
    - Baldwin School, Bryn Mawr College, commencement, 1988 (Box 101)
    - Roast of John Mack Carter, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Undated speeches
      - Remarks at Gael Greene lunch (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Speech at march against pornography (Box 101)
      - Speech at International Women's Year event (Box 101)
      - "Women as a Political Force" address before the League of Women Voters (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Women, the Law, and the Economy (Box 101)
      - Introduction of Alice Walker (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - "On Being a Writer" (Box 101)
      - Testimony before Human Rights Commission (Box 101)
      - Wedding remarks, Clarence and Dorothy (Box 101)
    - Radio and television
      - Spectrum (CBS program), 1977
        - Steinem's scripts (Box 102, Folder 1)
        - Commentaries by others (includes M. Stanton Evans, Nicholas Von Hoffman, Murray Kempton, Ethel Payne, Vincent Royster and Phyllis Schlafly) (Box 102, Folder 2-7)
        - Correspondence and notes from CBS (Box 102, Folder 8)
        - Texts, drafts, and notes of commentaries by Steinem, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - In Conversation With...
        [* indicates accompanying tape in SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL]
        - General correspondence, 1982-84 (Box 102, Folder 10)
        - Subject files: clippings, question lists, correspondence, transcripts, 1982-84
          - Asner, Ed (Box 102, Folder 11)
          - Bond, Julian (Box 102, Folder 12)
          - Brown, Helen Gurley (includes interview) * (Box 102, Folder 13)
          - Cronkite, Walter (Box 102, Folder 14)
          - Donahue, Phil (includes interview)* (Box 102, Folder 15)
          - Ford, Betty (includes interview) * (Box 102, Folder 16)
          - Galbraith, John Kenneth (includes interview) (Box 103, Folder 1)
          - Morrison, Toni (Box 103, Folder 2)
          - Naisbitt, John (Box 103, Folder 3)
            [see SERIES IV. WRITINGS- Article research files]
          - Ride, Sally (includes interview) * (Box 103, Folder 4)
          - Young, Andrew (Box 103, Folder 5)
          - Walker, Alice* (Box 103, Folder 6)
        - The Today Show
          - Clippings, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 7)
          - Financial materials: checks and invoices, 1986-88 (Box 103, Folder 8)
          - Itineraries, 1986-87 (Box 103, Folder 9)
          - Programs (includes "Backstage at Today," scriptundated; partial transcript of interview with Robert Redford, and transcript of interview with Wendy McCarthy) (Box 103, Folder 10-12)
          - Story ideas, 1987; undated (Box 103, Folder 13)
- SERIES IV. WRITINGS, 1957-97
  Throughout her career, Steinem has considered herself first and foremost a writer. This series documents her development as a journalist and author from her earliest publications as a graduate of Smith College to her recent best-selling books. It is arranged in six subseries: General, Press statements, Scripts, Articles, Books, and Unpublished work.
  General includes legal documents related to the publishing industry. Permissions to reprint or quote from Steinem's work are filed chronologically. This subseries also includes materials pertaining to Steinem's editorial work for Ladies Home Journal (where in 1964-65 she edited the "Metropolitan" section) and Warner Modular Communications (where in 1973 Steinem, together with Lenore Weitzman and Sheila Tobias, served on the editorial board for women's studies research).
  Several folders document Steinem's 1977-78 tenure at the Woodrow Wilson Center. She received a fellowship to consider "the longterm implications of feminism." Though her fellowship did not in fact result in the book she had initially envisioned, some of the essays which later appeared in Outrageous Acts and Everyday Rebellions resulted from her work at the Center, most notably the article on female genital mutilation co-authored with Robin Morgan.
  Finally, also filed here are endorsements, or "blurbs," for books, films and television shows. Endorsements, occasionally accompanied by correspondence, are filed alphabetically by the author's last name, or, where appropriate, the director or producer.
  Press statements on national events issued by Steinem's office, include, for example, the "unjust plight of Office Workers Local 174;" the Marvin v. Marvin palimony decision, women's registration for the draft, and so forth. Finally, drafts of several Scripts authored by Steinem in the late 1960s and early 1970s are housed here.
  The subseries containing Steinem's many Articles includes research files, texts and manuscripts. Articles are filed in alphabetical order by title. Folders may include a manuscript, typescript, galley, published version, or some combination thereof. Materials pertaining to the television movie that was developed from the article "A Bunny's Tale" follow the material pertaining to the article, filed here. The series also contains a bound volume of Help! (August 1960-February 1962), a "picture-humor magazine designed to frequently titillate the senses and occasionally tickle the mind," for which Steinem was contributing editor. For Steinem's regular articles published in Ms. magazine, researchers are referred to the magazine's bound volumes in the Sophia Smith Collection's periodical collection.
  Steinem's article research files, which follow the texts of the articles themselves, are arranged alphabetically by subject, and include transcripts of interviews with Fannie Lou Hamer, James Earl Jones, Shirley MacLaine, and John Naisbitt and Patricia Aburdene, among others.
  The subseries pertaining to Steinem's several Books is arranged alphabetically by title, and includes The Beach Book, Marilyn, Moving Beyond Words, Outrageous Acts and Everyday Rebellions, and WonderWoman. Materials include correspondence, legal papers, publicity, research files, and reviews, as well as the drafts, galleys and publications themselves.
  Finally, Unpublished work includes drafts of a travel guide, "India by Air," and some short fragments of texts.
  - General
    - Bibliographies of Steinem's writings (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Permissions
      - 1970-93 (Box 104, Folder 2-11)
      - 1994-97, undated (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
    - Reprints, undated (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Endorsements ["blurbs"] of work by others
      - A-Q (Box 105, Folder 6-10)
      - R-Z (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
    - The Rape of Inez Garcia: Legal correspondence, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Editorial work
    - Ladies Home Journal: correspondence, notes, and memoranda, 1964-65; undated (Box 106, Folder 4-5)
    - Warner Modular Communications: correspondence, memoranda, modules, permissions, and reprints, 1966-73 (Box 106, Folder 6-8)
  - Wilson Center Fellowship
    [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL-Financial and legal records, for related expenses]
    - Application materials, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 106, Folder 10-11)
    - Fellows handbook, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - General 1977-78 (includes evaluation) (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda, 1977-78 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Research materials, 1975-78; undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Press statements by Gloria Steinem, undated (Box 107, Folder 4-6)
  - Scripts, screenplays and film treatments
    - "Cally": correspondence, draft, and fragments, 1967-68 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - "Emma": screenplay, 1971; undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - "Polly": script, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - "That Was the Year that Was": contract, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - "Wonderwoman" (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Articles
    - Bound volume of Help!, 1960-61 (Box 108)
    - Texts, alphabetically by title: may include drafts, galleys, and/or publications
      [See complete title list of articles]
      - Adventures of Max and Jennie, Glamour, 1966; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Advice for Misfits, Glamour, Sep 1967; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - After Black Power What? Women's Liberation, That's What, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Age of the Contraceptive Pill, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - And Starring Lee Bouvier, McCall's, Feb 1968; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - The Anti-Woman Crusade to Houston, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Are we Open to Change?, Life Advertiser, Mar 1975; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - Barbra Streisand: The Beautiful Ugly Duckling, Ladies Home Journal, 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - The Beatle with a Future, Cosmopolitan, Dec 1964; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Begin to Say Goodbye Again, Secretary Speakout '81, 1981; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Best Christmas Gift of All: Tradition, Glamour, Sep 1966; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 11)
      - Bette Midler Ms. Woman of the Year, Oct 1987; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Big Weekend in New York, Esquire, Sep 1961; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 13)
      - The Black John Wayne: Jim Brown, New York, Nov 1968; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 14)
      - Book reviews 1966-68, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 15)
      - Boy-Girl Morals Quiz, Glamour, May 1966; 1 folders (Box 109, Folder 16)
      - A Bunny's Tale (includes materials related to both the article and the television movie adapted from it), 1963; 11 folders (Box 110, Folder 1-11)
      - But Dear God, Where are the Women?, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Charles Percy, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Cheer Up, Ms., Jul 1976; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - City on the Eve of Destruction, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - City Politics, columns for New York, 1968-76; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Clear and Present Difference, Ms., circa 1977; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - A Close-up Look at Bernadette Devlin, Glamour, 1968; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Coalition for Full Employment, Social Policy, Sep 1974; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - College and What I Learned There, Glamour, Aug 1964; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Comfort, Glamour, Feb 1963; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 10)
      - Coming of Age with McGovern, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 11)
      - Coming Up: The Unprecedented Woman, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 12)
      - Commentary Corner, Advertising Age, 1984; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 13)
      - Communist Concerns of Womankind, World Paper, Jul-Aug 1980; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 14)
      - Communist Party of India, Smith College paper[?], 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 15)
      - The Contraceptive Revolution and the Single Girl, 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 16)
      - Crazylegs; or, the Biography of Fashion, New York Times Magazine, Dec 1964; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 17)
      - Culture and the Candidates, Glamour, Dec 1964; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 18)
      - The Death of the Cool and the Birth of Beyond Cool, Glamour, Dec 1964; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 19)
      - Deception, Glamour, May 1965; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 20)
      - Detroit Press Blackout, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 21)
      - Do You Know about These Trends?, 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 22)
      - The Draft: Ms. Shoots Back, Electricity, 20 Mar 1980; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 23)
      - The Draft: Who Needs It, 1980; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 24)
      - Editorial, Ms. 5th Birthday, 1977; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 25)
      - Editorial, Ms. 15th Birthday, 1987; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 26)
      - Erotica and Pornography: a Clear and Present Difference, Ms., Nov 1978; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 27)
      - Erotica vs. Pornography: What's the Difference? Sunday Woman, circa Nov 1978; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 28)
      - The Establishment Lives (More or Less), n.d.; 1 folders (Box 111, Folder 29)
      - Eureka! Europa, Show, May 1962; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Family Portraits, 1989; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - The Fate of Zsa Zsa's Bed, New York, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - The Ferraro Factor, Ms., Oct 1984; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - First Lie Detector, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - First Take the Ms. College Quiz, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Flash of Power, Ms., Feb 1978; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Frontis, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - Funny Ways to Find a Man on the Beach, Glamour, Jun 1963; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - [Galley No. 1], Ms., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 10)
      - Gernreich's Progress; or, Eve Unbound, New York Times Magazine, Jan 1965; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 11)
      - Girls in Their Summer Dresses, Glamour, May 1964; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - Glenda Jackson on Sarah Bernhardt, Ms., Feb 1976; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 13)
      - Gloria Steinem Frontispiece, Ms., 28 Apr 1985; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 14)
      - Gloria Steinem on Chivalry, Mainliner, Feb 1975; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 15)
      - Glora Steinem and Elizabeth Reid on Revolution, 1976; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 16)
      - Go Right Ahead and Ask Me Anything, McCall's, Nov 1967; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 17)
      - Going Too Far, review of Robin Morgan's book, New York Times Book Review, 6 May 1977; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 18)
      - G.Q. Tests, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 19)
      - Great Establishment Game, Glamour, Jul 1967; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 20)
      - Gro Harlem Brundtland Ms. Woman of the Year, 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 21)
      - Haircut by Sassoon, Glamour, Mar 1964; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 23)
      - Happy Birthday Card from Ms., n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 24)
      - Helsinki: The Last Red Festival, Show, Oct 1962; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 25)
      - Ho Chi Minh in New York, New York, Apr 1968; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 26)
      - How Far Behind the Scenes Can You Get?, Show, Mar 1962; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 27)
      - How I Became a Writer, Glamour, Oct 1985; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 28)
      - How I Work When I Work, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 29)
      - How Not to Feel Morally Inferior to the French, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 30)
      - How the Single Girl Really Spends Her Money Glamour, Oct 1963; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 31)
      - How to Find Your Type, Glamour, Feb 1964; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 32)
      - How to Know Which Men to Pick Up, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 33)
      - How to Leave Home Gracefully, Glamour, Mar 1965; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 34)
      - How to Pick up a Man on the Beach, n.d.; 1 folders (Box 112, Folder 35)